Review exercise two, are you steadfast or freewheeling? Answer the following
questions with a check mark in the appropriate box. Number one, would you
rather answer an essay question or a multiple choice question? Number two, do
you start from yes or start from no? Number three, do you prefer solutions that
are open-ended, abstract, and subject to interpretation or clear-cut, precise, and
objective? Number four, are you comfortable with a flexible time frame
with constant updates or more deadline-oriented? Number five, do you prefer to
follow another person's lead or do things your own way? If you selected the second
option two or more times, try this experiment. Just for today, when someone
says something to you, practice temporarily suspending judgment. Respond
with, hmm, that's interesting. Tell me more or you could be right. Not only will
this help you listen better, it will also make you a better conversationalist and
open your mind to picking up and using this accent.